You're good at games, I'll give you that.
I enjoy the maze part, the eating without eating part.
Packed-outs are calorie-free.
What's the verdict on the Prince Intelligence?
Science and technical officers, sir.
I'm sorry.
It's ten years ahead of anything we have in the field.
So you think the Colonel's for real?
US intelligence would never give up anything that's valuable as part of the trap.
Philip and I both question Prince's motives.
He says $50,000 is his motive.
I think that's believable.
I think how much Prince could get from the FBI for delivering a directorate as officer to them.
He'd be swimming in very deep water.
He doesn't strike me as the type.
The FBI could be behind it without Prince being aware.
They could be controlling the sources of information.
I think that's believable.
The FBI could be behind it without Prince being aware.
They could be controlling the source and waiting for a meeting to be set up with the Colonel.
A meeting has been set.
The Colonel put the time and location for us on a microton.
He also said the technical information he sent was just to prove he's for real.
He says that he has something truly vital for us, but he can only get that to us in person.
A trap is always a possibility, but in this case it's worth the risk.
It's easy to say from the sidelines.
Don't get your panties in a bunch, Elizabeth. This isn't about you and me.
The Center wants the meeting with the Colonel to proceed.
I don't trust a word that bitch says. I mean, who knows what she could be up to.
So let's con-